Now that we know the general change we want to make,
现在我们已经大概了解了想进行的变更
we need to choose a metric to measure that change.
我们需要选择一个指标来测量这个变更
For the current version of our hypothesis, we didn't really talk about
在当前的假设中 我们还没有谈及
how to measure whether changing the color scheme was an improvement.
如何测量改变颜色是否真的是一种改进
What Audacity ultimately cares about is how many people actually complete
而 Audacity 在意的归根究底还是有多少人
courses, so one possible metric is total number of courses completed.
完成了课程 所以可以选择完成课程的数量作为指标
However, given that it can take students weeks or months to finish courses,
然而学生可能需要几周或几个月的时间才能完成课程
using this metric would simply take too much time to be practical.
采用这个作为指标的话会耗费太多时间了 不太现实
An alternative is how many users actually click on the Start Now button.
另外一个选择就是有多少用户实际点击了 现在开始 这个按钮
The assumption is that if more people click the button and
在我们的设想中 如果更多的人点击了这个按钮
thus move on to exploring the site, then eventually,
然后进一步地探索这个网站
some of them will create an account and go on to complete a course.
最终 其中的一部分人会创建账号 完成课程
In other words, increasing the rate at which users progress down the funnel at
也就是说 增加用户从第一层往下走的几率
one level will have a positive impact on the end of the funnel as well.
会对漏斗的最终结果有正面的影响
Can you think of any problems with counting clicks?
你能想到计算点击时会有什么问题么？
What happens if more total users view the page in one version of
如果某个实验版本的用户浏览总数更高
the experiment?
那会怎么样？
Suppose these dots are the total number of visitors in each group of
假设这些点是实验中每一组的总访客数
the experiment, and the yellow dots are the ones who clicked.
黄色的点代表点击了按钮的人
More total clicks occurred in this version, but
这个版本中总点击数更高
there was a greater percentage of clicks in this version.
但这个版本中 点击百分比更高
So instead, we could use the fraction of page visitors who click.
所以 我们可以使用访客点击页面的比例
That is the number of clicks on the view course's button
也就是点击课程按钮的数量
divided by the number of page views to the home page.
除以主页访问的数量
This metric is commonly called click-through rate, or CTR.
这个指标一般称为点击率
There's also a closely related metric which many people also refer to as
另外还有一个关系相近的指标 人们也称为点击率
click-through rate, but I'll call it click-through probability.
但我这里称它为点击概率
Click-through probability is defined as the number of unique visitors who click
点击概率是至少点击一次的独立访客数量
at least once divided by the number of unique visitors who view the page.
除以浏览页面的独立访客数量
To see how these two metrics are different,
让我们来看看这两个指标的区别
suppose you have a webpage and two users visit the homepage.
假设你有一个主页 然后两个用户访问了主页
The first leaves without clicking the Start Now button,
第一个没有点击 现在开始 按钮就离开了
which means they clicked 0 times.
也就是说点击 0 次
And the second person clicks 5 times.
而第二个人点击了 5 次
Maybe the next page loaded slowly, so the user impatiently clicked 5 times.
可能下一个页面载入很慢 这个用户不耐烦 点击了 5 次
In this case, the click-through rate equals 2.5,
这样的话 点击率等于 2.5
since there were 5 total clicks and 2 total page views.
因为有 5 次点击 2 个页面访问
But the click-through probability equals 0.5,
但是点击概率等于 0.5
since half the users who visited the page clicked.
因为访问这个页面的用户的一半点击了按钮
Rates and probabilities have different characteristics,
比率与概率有不同的特点
which we'll talk about further in lesson three.
我们会在第三课中进一步讨论
For the purpose of this lesson, we're going to use click click-through
本课中 我们将使用点击概率
probability as our metric, and not click-through rate.
作为指标 而不是点击率
Given this, our updated hypothesis
因此 我们更新后的假设为
is that we will increase the click-through probability of the button.
我们将提高按钮的点击概率
And we assume that that will ultimately increase the final business metric,
我们还假设这会最终提高终极业务指标
which is total courses completed
即完成课程的总数